<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FirebaseQuizApp</string>
    <string name="create_quiz_info">In case the image for the quiz is not picked,a color can be picked if both of them are not picked then a color will be randomly selected for the quiz</string>
    <string name="image_extra">Pick an image for the quiz,just for visual representation</string>
    <string name="contribute_quiz_info">You can not only answers quizzes in this app. But you can too contribute some quizzes over hear.</string>
    <string name="profile_info">Change your profile settings from here, There aren\'t much options for now.</string>
    <string name="profile_info_note">The changes applied to the user are not directly shown in the app. SO see the changes,restart your app</string>
    <string name="quiz_tab_info">Here are the available quiz\'s that one can participate in.Click one to participate in it</string>
    <string name="home_tab_card_info">Enter the quiz Id to directly participate in the quiz. Make sure its approved</string>
    <string name="adding_question_wait">Adding the questions and there respective options to the database please wait</string>
    <string name="create_quiz_desc">Know a certain topic,want to contribute a quiz for that,add the quiz details and add the questions</string>
    <string name="create_quiz_dialog_text">Quiz has been added to the database you now can add the questions to the quiz</string>
    <string name="all_quizzes_extra_info">If certain quiz are not found,that means they aren\'t approved yet,or they lost there approval</string>
    <string name="quiz_submition_desc">Your results will be added to the database, you can visit the results section to view the results</string>
    <string name="results_desc">How did you perform in your last attempts ? Lets take a look at your results</string>
    <string name="results_not_found">Our records indicate that you haven\'t participated in ant of the quizzes.Take a quiz to test your knowledge</string>
    <string name="add_quiz_question_text">Create your own unique quizzes and challenge your knowledge.Put your knowledge on display today</string>
    <string name="list_questions_title">Provided below is a comprehensive and exhaustive list of all the question that have been compiled</string>
    <string name="list_questions_addtional">At the moment it\'s possible to delete questions but updating them is not currently an available option</string>
    <string name="delete_full_quiz_desc">Deleting this quiz will delete all the questions along with the results associated with the quiz</string>
</resources>